We're gonna wake it in for the brand new world
Yeah
We're gonna take you to the brand new world
To the brand new world
We're gonna wake it in for the brand new world
Get your hands up, baby
We're gonna take you to the brand new world
They drowned out
Get it on, get it on,始めよう
難航不楽のリアリティ
立ち止まる時間はないさ
Hold on, hold on
Now this time, fight for liberty
真実性 飲み込み常識
欲求の先にある朝
Oh yeah
幻想に埋もれた人生の夢
Hands up
Shout it, shout it louder
Yes, do it, do it, start it
Never give up
限界を超えても
勝つくしていく
Feel it
We're gonna face
Let's go, whoa
Leave it myself
衝動的に突き進め
Don't be afraid
誰よりも高く飛べ
Take it to the sky
想像を超えた世界をこの手に
The ground up
想像さ
偽りどない一連の道
Yes
It's a ground up
Hey yeah
Believe in myself
Believe in yourself
Hey yeah
Yeah
The ground up
Devils are born in the underworld
From the first breath you take
You have a spot in the pecking order
And it's impossible to change it
Since I was born with no magic
Obviously I was at the bottom
I spent every day covered in my own blood
You're so pitiful it's not even fun to beat you up
If only that didn't exist
Every devil wishes they could cross over into the human world
But the underworld gate stops them from getting through
So to pass the time
The strong oppress the weak
And the weak oppress anyone weaker than they are
That's how shitty things are there
Go on and cry
Scream for mercy like always
I didn't care about anything
Not even whether I lived or died
You brat
What's so funny
I figured I would crash into the gate
And my body would shatter
But since I didn't have any magic
I slipped right through
And before I knew it
I ended up in the human world
Maybe it was because I was helpless
Or because I was exhausted from all the beatings
But I didn't care one way or the other about humans
Still
Over there
It's got horns
Could it be
The devil
Can curse us
Someone call the magic knife
It didn't take long for humans with powerful magic to find and attack me
My body started shutting down
I was ready to accept my death
Finally
This pointless life will be over forever
You're awake?
Thank goodness
My name is Lichita
It's nice to meet you
I figured you'd be safer at my house
It's okay
You can relax
No one knows you're here
So they won't come looking for you
I just used my magic ability
If something doesn't have mana
I can use my ability to put it into and take it out of things
I found you while I was out gathering some firewood
So I just popped you in this bottle
You can imagine how shocked I was
I mean, just the other day I found this five leaf grimoire
But stumbling across a devil was an even bigger surprise than that
You're weird
Shouldn't you be more afraid of me?
Why would I be afraid of a little boy who's all beat up?
After all, it's not like you have any magic
Yeah, but all humans hate devils, don't they?
Sure, people might hate you, but you're not the only one
You see? My body saps magic and life away from anything that gets too close to me
I can't help it
That's why I live alone
I keep my distance from the village so I don't bother anyone
But luckily, you don't have any mana
And it doesn't look like I'm draining your life either
I guess it's because you're a devil?
It's gotta be destiny
I know, maybe I should adopt you
Adopt me?
A human raising a devil as her own?
I couldn't wrap my head around it at all
But...
Come on, we gotta hurry up!
Alright! Hello dinner!
That human...
It's so pretty!
I couldn't believe she would open her heart to someone like me
A devil born with no magic in a dark, hopeless pit
Who cursed my own existence
That woman changed my whole world for the better
Just because you're a devil, that doesn't automatically mean that you're some kind of evil being at heart
Trust me
I know for sure you're not a bad guy
Thanks to you, I don't have to live my whole life all alone
You saved me, Leba
Leba
I saved you?
Leba, what's wrong?
Are you okay?
Leba
My name
Is Luciferous
I never thought I would find a devil out here in the human world who hadn't made a contract with anyone yet
So I'm glad I took the time to look around
That's one of the highest ranked devils
He's taking control of my body
Must be my lucky day
If I play my cards right, I'm sure there's a way I can use this weakling to manifest my own body in this world
That's enough! Get out of Leba's body right now!
What a foolish woman
I may not have full use of my powers, but you're still a match for me
She is training my mama
I suppose you have a death wish
You're going to pay
Don't hurt her
You won't win
I won't let go
Not this time
I won't let you
You're not taking
My side
Impossible
To think a mere human could get in my way
No matter
I could never be the lower devil anywhere
I shall return in time
Leech
Are you?
You?
I'm sorry
I guess
I'm kind of stupid
This was the only way I could think of to protect you from that horrible monster
Monster, I'll use my magic to seal you into this five-leaf grimoire, where you'll be safe.
By the time someone releases you from it, I'm sure you'll have gotten a lot bigger and stronger.
Please, Lima, live, okay?
I love you, my sweet little boy.
But, but, but, but...
Look, loser! Just hand over the body already!
His key, it's full of anger and hatred and sadness.
I'm sure you have your reasons, just like I do.
I'll try to accept that, and figure out what you're so mad about, and then I'll win!
You gotta be kidding me, you idiot!
You really think you could beat me with one arm?
Yeah, you heard me!
I still got plenty of muscle!
The devil fights with anti-magic, which is primarily used to nullify an opponent's magic power.
Since Asta doesn't have any, it's not much of a threat to him.
But...
I'm not gonna lose to a pathetic human like you!
Captain Yami's Kitana!
Without my anti-magic, those swords are useless!
They're just hunks of steel!
I don't give a damn about your physical strength!
You're screwed!
No magic means no spatial transfer!
So you can't break this blade!
How could you stand a chance against a high-ranked devil, if you can't even hold your own in a fight with me?
Stop kidding yourself!
After that, I was sealed away within the five-leaf grimoire, with no means of escape.
They're gonna pay for this!
I'll kill them!
All of them!
I spent all my time cursing Lucifero and the other devils.
And then, I gained the power of anti-magic.
The power to nullify spells.
This is it!
This is how I'll get my revenge!
One day, the five-leaf grimoire chose a human to become its master.
As luck would have it, this kid was born with no magic, too.
I realized that if I ever wanted to go back out into the human world, the only way was for me to use him as a host.
I'd take over his entire body if I had to.
In case you haven't figured it out, every devil is an evil piece of shit!
Which is exactly why I'll personally make sure every last one of them is destroyed!
And I'll use your body to do it!
I'll let my hatred run wild and kill them all!
You know something, pal?
I think I finally understand you.
So that's how you feel.
Thanks for letting me know.
Huh?
What do you say?
Look, just give up!
You can't use magic or anti-magic now!
You're history!
But I still dodged your swords!
All I had to do was focus on reading your key, big guy.
It's true.
I don't have any magic.
And without you, I don't even have anti-magic.
But I've got the will to win.
And my unbreakable bonds with all the amazing people I've met.
Yuno and I were taken in by the church in Hodge Village on the same day.
And I didn't have one bit of mana.
Yuno is cooler than me, and he's smarter than me.
But he's still my rival.
We decided we would compete to see who'd become the Wizard King.
Having him in my life is what inspired me to keep getting better.
Then I met Captain Yami at the entrance exam, and I joined the Black Bulls.
And without them, I wouldn't be the person I am today.
And it's not just them.
I've met lots of people.
Friends and enemies.
There were a lot of tough battles.
A few of the opponents I fought became my friends after it was all over.
Some of them didn't.
But I won't forget a single one of them.
Because each of those people are a part of me.
And they always will be.
Get results.
Prove that you're the strongest.
It takes you so long to do everything, Asta.
Hurry up.
I'm gonna need backup over here.
Asta!
No way.
Even after the Five-Leaf Grimoire showed up, and I figured out that I could use anti-magic, I trained.
I wanted to be as strong as all those amazing fighters I met.
Better than them, even. The good guys and the bad guys.
I kept pushing past my limits!
Whoa!
Don't tell me that was the best you could do, Austin.
I know you're capable of more than that.
Let's go!
Right!
No matter how hard you train, your body still has limits.
You don't stand a chance the way you are now. But all that work may just pay off.
I'm a human with no magic. But that's not all you're up against when you face me. I fought with a whole bunch of powerful warriors, and each one of them taught me something new!
No!
A human won't stop me! Not after how much I cursed them! I was all alone!
I was all alone!
No!
Well done!
Huh?
The preparations for the ritual are now complete!
The next step is establishing a contract with your Devil, giving you total control over him.
This part's easy! Simply think obey me, and from this moment on, you'll have a devoted familiar to aid you and follow your endeavors.
Every command. That's the only way to become the ultimate warrior.
Okay. Then...
Starting right now, we should be friends!
What's the matter? Devils don't even know what a friend is? Okay, I'll try to explain. It's like, uh...
Hold on a second. Are you attempting to create an equal contract with your Devil?
Yep.
I mentioned this earlier, but I never could have made it this far without his help.
The thing is, I never stopped to learn anything about him.
Even though he's been with me for such a long time, if we're gonna keep working together, we need to become friends.
What are you talking about? There's no guarantee that this Devil will pay you any heed at all.
Do you expect that contract to work? There's nothing binding about it.
It's fine. I could tell from the beginning he wasn't fighting me for real.
He kept talking about killing me, but I knew he was holding back.
You can't kill anybody, can you?
What you can do is get angry for someone else's sake.
That's why we'd get along. You and I should work together as equals.
This isn't a devil-binding ritual. It's a... uh... a devil-befriending ritual.
Not the sharpest knife in the drawer, is he, Mr. Nogt?
It appears not.
If you ask me, it sounds like we've got the same enemies.
So what do you say to forming a team with me, right now?
This is nuts. I never knew anyone could be as stupid as you are.
I'm still not sure if destiny is real, but...
Oh, by the way, you haven't told me your name yet.
What do you mean?
You don't have one? That's okay. I'll pick one out for you.
Hmm.
Ah! Liba. Starting today, your name's Liba.
There's no doubt about it.
He's leeched us, kid.
You can call me... Liba.
Whoa, what's that?
I finally got my own back!
Thank you so much, buddy!
The contract is complete.
I must admit, you've done something truly unprecedented.
I didn't expect such a foolish move, even from you.
However, you made the right choice.
Still, though, being right doesn't always mean you'll be rewarded.
That's why you need strength.
To keep evil from prevailing.
You have two days.
Think you can become the strongest?
Yeah!
Lord, Pechka, I'll save you, no matter what.
Okay!
Let's get ready!
We can win.
Even if they're crazy strong.
We'll push past our limits.
Because we're the Black Bulls!
Isn't that right, Yami?
Do you know where I'm supposed to be?
Wherever you go...
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I'm training as hard as I can to beat Xenon, but I'm not getting the results I need.
You can stop hiding. Just come out here already.
I figure it might be useful to have a spatial magic user to spar with.
After all, it's only fair of me to help you with your training, right?
Trust me, I'd much prefer to handle it myself, but this is something that affects the whole Golden Dawn.
I know you've improved your skills, too, so I'll accept your offer.
I see you're still an insolent brat, but at least you're more straightforward now.
Oh, I'm going to save Captain Vongence.
All right! Hang in there, Captain Yami!
No matter how tough they are, I'll take them down.
I'm going to keep our kingdom and the whole world safe.
In this place where magic is everything, there lives one boy who was born without it.
However, despite the many challenges he faces, Asta works hard and refuses to give up.
He and his childhood rival train through blood, sweat, and tears,
in hopes of one day becoming the next Wizard King.